<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.calligra</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Calligra</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligraxx</name>
  <summary>All-in-one office solution</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Solució d'oficina tot en un</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Solució d'oficina tot en un</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Solución ofimática todo en uno</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bulego soluzioa, dena batean</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Solución de oficina todo en un.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">פתרון משרדי אחוד</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Soluzione per ufficio completa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">სრული საოფისე პაკეტი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Viss vienā biroja programmatūra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Alles-in-een kantooroplossing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Rozwiązanie biurowe wszystko-w-jednym</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Pisarniška rešitev vse v enem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Allt i ett kontorslösning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Hepsi bir arada ofis çözümü</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Універсальне офісне рішення</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxAll-in-one office solutionxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Calligra is an office and graphics suite. It contains applications for word processing, spreadsheets, presentation and vector graphics.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Calligra és una suite d'oficina i gràfics. Conté aplicacions per a processament de textos, fulls de càlcul, presentacions i gràfics vectorials.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Calligra és una suite d'oficina i gràfics. Conté aplicacions per a processament de textos, fulls de càlcul, presentacions i gràfics vectorials.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Calligra es un paquete ofimático y gráfico. Contiene aplicaciones para procesamiento de textos, hojas de cálculo, presentaciones y gráficos vectoriales.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Calligra bulegotika eta grafikoen suite bat da. Testua prozesatzeko, kalkulu-orriak, aurkezpen eta bektore-grafikoak ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Calligra e unha suite de oficina e de gráficos. Contén aplicacións para procesamento de texto, follas de cálculo, presentacións e gráficos vectoriais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Calligra היא חבילה של כלים משרדיים וגרפיים. היא מכילה יישומים לעיבוד תמלילים, גיליונות נתונים, מצגות וגרפיקת וקטורים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Calligra è una suite per ufficio e grafica. Contiene applicazioni per elaborazione testi, fogli di calcolo, presentazioni e grafica vettoriale.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Calligra საოფისე და გრაფიკული პროგრამების პაკეტია. შეიცავს ტექსტის დასამუშავებელ. ელცხრილებთან სამუშაო, პრეზენტაციის ქმნის და ვექტორული გრაფიკის პროგრამებს.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Calligra“ ir biroja un grafikas programmatūra. Tā satur programmas teksta, izklājlapu, prezentācijas un vektorgrafikas apstrādei.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Calligra is een suite voor kantoor en grafische zaken. Het bevat toepassingen voor tekstbewerking, rekenbladen, presentatie en vectorgrafiek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Calligra jest pakietem biurowym i graficznym. Zawiera aplikacje do przetwarzania tekstu, arkuszy kalkulacyjnych, prezentacji oraz grafiki wektorowej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Calligra je pisarniški in grafični paket. Vsebuje aplikacije za obdelavo besedil, preglednic, predstavitev in vektorsko grafiko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Calligra är en kontors- och grafiksvit. Den innehåller program för ordbehandling, kalkylblad, presentation och vektorgrafik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Calligra bir ofis ve grafik paketidir. Sözcük işleme, tablolar, sunum ve vektör grafikler için araçlar içerir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Calligra — комплект офісних і графічних програм. У ньому містяться програми для роботи з текстом, електронними таблицями, презентаціями та векторною графікою.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra is an office and graphics suite. It contains applications for word processing, spreadsheets, presentation and vector graphics.xx</p>
    <!-- Word -->
    <p>
      Words is an intuitive word processor and desktop publisher application.
      With it, you can create informative and attractive documents with pleasure and ease.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Words és una aplicació intuïtiva de procés de textos i de publicació d'escriptori. Amb ella es poden crear documents informatius i atractius amb satisfacció i facilitat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Words és una aplicació intuïtiva de procés de textos i de publicació d'escriptori. Amb ella es poden crear documents informatius i atractius amb satisfacció i facilitat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Words es un procesador de textos intuitivo y una aplicación de edición para el escritorio. Con ella se pueden crear documentos informativos y atractivos de forma placentera y con facilidad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Words, testu-prozesatzaile eta argitaratzeko mahaigaineko aplikazio intuitibo bat da. Hori erabiliz, dokumentu informatibo eta erakargarriak sor ditzakezu, erraz eta aise.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Words é unha aplicación intuitiva de procesamento de texto e publicación de escritorio. Con ela pode crear documentos informativos e atractivos plácida e facilmente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">„מילים” הוא יישום נהיר למחשב לעיבוד תמלילים והפקת תוכן. באמצעותו, אפשר ליצור מסמכים רבי משמעות ומושכי עין בצורה מהנה ופשוטה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Words è un'applicazione intuitiva per l'elaborazione di testi e l'editoria desktop. Con essa, puoi creare documenti informativi e accattivanti con piacere e facilità.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Words ინტუიტიური ტექსტის პროცესორი და ამუშაო მაგიის გამომცემლის აპლიკაციაა. მასთან ერთად შეგიძლიათ ინფორმატიული და მიმზიდველი დოკუმენტები სიამოვნებითა და ადვილად შექმნათ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Words“ ir intuitīva teksta apstrādes un datorizdevniecības programma. Ar to varat patīkami un ērti veidot informatīvus un pievilcīgus dokumentus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Words is een intuïtieve toepassing voor tekstverwerken en weergeven op het bureaublad. Hiermee kunt u informatieve en attractieve documenten met plezier en gemak maken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Słowa jest intuicyjnym edytorem tekstu i biurkowym programem do publikowania. Dzięki niemu można tworzyć informacyjne i atrakcyjne dokumenty z łatwością użycia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Words je intuitiven urejevalnik besedil in aplikacija za namizne izdajatelje. Z njim lahko z užitkom in preprosto ustvarjate informativne in privlačne dokumente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Words är en intuitiv ordbehandlare och skrivbordspubliceringsprogram. Med den kan du skapa informativa och attraktiva dokument med nöje och lätthet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Calligra Sözcükler, sezgisel bir sözcük işlemcisi ve masaüstü yayım uygulamasıdır. Bununla, zevkle ve kolaylıkla bilgilendirici ve alımlı belgeler oluşturabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Words — інтуїтивно зрозуміла у користування програма для редагування текстів та приготування матеріалів для друку. За її допомогою ви можете створювати інформативні та візуально красиві документи із задоволенням та без напруження.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxWords is an intuitive word processor and desktop publisher application. With it, you can create informative and attractive documents with pleasure and ease.xx</p>
    <!-- Sheet -->
    <p>
      Calligra Sheets is a fully-featured calculation and spreadsheet tool.
      Use it to quickly create and calculate various business-related spreadsheets, such as income and expenditure, employee working hours, etc.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Sheets del Calligra és una eina de full de càlcul plenament funcional. S'usa per a crear i calcular ràpidament diversos fulls de càlcul relacionats amb els negocis, com els ingressos i despeses, les hores de treball dels empleats, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Sheets de Calligra és una eina de full de càlcul plenament funcional. S'utilitza per a crear i calcular ràpidament diversos fulls de càlcul relacionats amb els negocis, com els ingressos i despeses, les hores de treball dels empleats, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Calligra Sheets es una herramienta de cálculo y de hojas de cálculo rica en funciones. Puede usarla para calcular y crear rápidamente diversas hojas de cálculo empresariales, como las de gastos e ingresos, horas de trabajo de los empleados, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Calligra Sheets, kalkulatzeko tresna eta kalkulu-orri tresna guztiz funtzional bat da. Erabil ezazu negozioarekin lotutako hainbat kalkulu-orri azkar sortzeko eta kalkulatzeko, hala nola, diru-sarrerak eta gastuak, enplegatuen lanorduak, etab.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Calligra Sheets é unha ferramenta completa de follas de cálculo. Úsea para crear rapidamente follas de cálculo de negocios, como por exemplo follas de gastos e ingresos, de horas de traballo, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">גיליונות של Calligra הוא כלי חישוב וגיליון נתונים עתיר יכולות. אפשר להשתמש בו כדי ליצור ולחשב גיליונות נתונים עסקיים במהירות, כגון הכנסות והוצאות, שעות עבודה של עובדים ועוד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Calligra Sheets è uno strumento di calcolo e foglio di calcolo completo. Utilizzalo per creare e calcolare rapidamente vari fogli di calcolo aziendali, come entrate e uscite, ore di lavoro dei dipendenti, ecc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Callgra Sheets სრულაფსოვანი გამოთვლებისა და ელცხრილებთან სამუშაო პროგრამაა. გამოიყენეთ ის, რომ შექმნათ და გამოთვალოთ ბიზნესთან დაკავშირებული საჭიროებები. მაგალითად: შემოსავალ/გასავალი, თანამშრომლების სამუშაო საათები და ა.შ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Calligra Sheets“ ir iespējām bagāts aprēķinu un izklājlapu rīks. Izmantojiet „Sheets“, lai ātri izveidotu un aprēķinātu dažādas ar uzņēmējdarbību saistītas izklājlapas, piemēram, ienākumus, izdevumus, darbinieku darba stundas u.c. vajadzībām.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Calligra Sheets is een hulpmiddel voor rekenen en rekenblad rijk aan functies. Gebruik het om snel verschillende zakelijke rekenbladen te maken, zoals inkomsten en uitgaven, werkuren van werknemers, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Arkusze Calligra jest pełnowartościowym narzędziem arkusza kalkulacyjnego i obliczeń. Użyj go do szybkiego tworzenia i obliczania rozmaitych biznesowych arkuszy kalkulacyjnych, takich jak przychód i rozchód, godziny pracy pracowników, itp.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Calligra Sheets je popolnoma opremljeno orodje za izračune in preglednice. Uporabite gaza hitro ustvarjanje in izračun različnih preglednic, povezanih s poslovanjem, nprkot so prihodki in odhodki, delovni čas zaposlenih itd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Calligra Sheets är ett fullfjädrat beräknings- och kalkylverktyg. Använd det för att snabbt skapa och beräkna olika företagsrelaterade kalkylblad, såsom inkomster och utgifter, anställdas arbetstid etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Calligra Tablolar, tam özellikli bir hesaplama ve elektronik tablo aracıdır. Gelir ve gider, çalışan çalışma saatleri vb. gibi çeşitli iş ile ilgili elektronik tabloları hızla oluşturmak ve hesaplamak için kullanın.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Calligra Sheets — повноцінне середовище для обчислень та роботи з електронними таблицями. Програмою можна скористатися для швидкого створення та обчислень на різноманітних пов’язаних із бізнесом електронних таблицях, зокрема вхідних та вихідних рахунках, табелів робочого часу тощо.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Sheets is a fully-featured calculation and spreadsheet tool. Use it to quickly create and calculate various business-related spreadsheets, such as income and expenditure, employee working hours, etc.xx</p>
    <!-- Stage -->
    <p>
      Calligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application.
      You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system,
      so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility
      of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Stage del Calligra és una aplicació de presentació flexible i fàcil d'utilitzar. Podeu crear fàcilment presentacions que continguin una gran varietat d'elements, des de gràfics a text, des de diagrames a imatges. L'Stage del Calligra és ampliable mitjançant un sistema de connectors, de manera que és senzill afegir efectes nous, elements de contingut nous o inclús noves maneres de gestionar les presentacions. Gràcies a la integració amb el Calligra, tota la potència i la flexibilitat dels elements de contingut del Calligra estan disponibles per a l'Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Stage de Calligra és una aplicació de presentació flexible i fàcil d'utilitzar. Podeu crear amb facilitat presentacions que continguen una gran varietat d'elements, des de gràfics fins a text, des de diagrames fins a imatges. Stage de Calligra és ampliable mitjançant un sistema de connectors, de manera que és senzill afegir efectes nous, elements de contingut nous o inclús noves maneres de gestionar les presentacions. Gràcies a la integració amb Calligra, tota la potència i la flexibilitat dels elements de contingut de Calligra estan disponibles per a Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Calligra Stage es una aplicación de presentaciones fácil de usar, aunque flexible. Permite crear con facilidad presentaciones que contienen una rica variedad de elementos, desde gráficos hasta texto, y desde gráficas a imágenes. Calligra Stage se puede extender mediante un sistema de complementos, por lo que resulta fácil añadir nuevos efectos, nuevos elementos de contenido e incluso nuevas formas de gestionar la presentación. Debido a su integración con Calligra, toda la potencia y la flexibilidad de los elementos de Calligra están disponibles para Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«Calligra Stage» erabiltzeko erraza eta aldi berean malgua den aurkezpen aplikazio bat da. Erraz sor ditzakezu era askotako elementuak dituzten aurkezpenak, grafikoak nahiz testua, diagramak nahiz irudiak. «Calligra Stage» plugin sistema baten bidez heda daiteke, horregatik erraza da efektu berriak, eduki-elementu berriak edo baita zure aurkezpenak kudeatzeko era berriak gehitzea. «Calligra»rekiko integrazioaren ondorioz, «Calligra»ko eduki elementuen gaitasun eta malgutasun guztia «Stage»n erabilgarri daude.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Calligra Stage é unha aplicación de presentacións fácil de usar pero flexíbel. Permítelle crear presentacións cunha ampla variedade de elementos, incluíndo texto, gráficos e imaxes. As funcionalidades de Calligra Stage poden ampliarse mediante un sistema de complementos, así que resulta doado engadir efectos e elementos novos, así como novos xeitos de xestionar as presentacións. Grazas á súa integración con Calligra, Stage pode facer uso da potencia e flexibilidade dos elementos de contido dispoñíbeis en Calligra.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Calligra במה הוא יישום מצגות קל לשימוש ועדיין מאוד גמיש. אפשר בקלות ליצור מצגות שמכילות מגוון רחב של רכיבים, החל מגרפיקה דרך טקסט וכלה בתמונות. את Calligra במה אפשר להרחיב בעזרת מערכת תוספים, כך שקל להוסיף אפקטים חדשים, רכיבי תוכן חדשים או איפלו דרכים חדשות לנהל את הצגת המצגת שלך. בזכות השילוב מול Calligra, כל העוצמה והגמישות של רכיבי התוכן של Calligra זמינים בבמה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Calligra Stage è un'applicazione di presentazione facile da utilizzare, ma comunque flessibile. Puoi creare facilmente presentazioni contenenti un'ampia varietà di elementi, dalla grafica al testo, dai grafici alle immagini. Calligra Stage è ampliabile tramite un sistema di estensioni, quindi è facile aggiungere nuovi effetti, nuovi elementi di contenuto o persino nuovi modi di gestire la tua presentazione. Grazie all'integrazione con Calligra, tutta la potenza e la flessibilità degli elementi di contenuto di Calligra sono disponibili per Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Calligra Stage უადვილესი პრეზენტაციის აპლიკაციაა. შექმენით ადვილად პრეზენტაციები, რომლებიც შეიცავენ მრავალფეროვან ელემენტებს, გრაფიკიდან ტექსტამდე, გრაფიკებიდან გამოსახულებებამდე. Calligra Stage გაფართოებადია დამატებების სისტემით, ასე რომ, ახალი ეფექტების, ახალი შემცველობის ელემენტების და თქვენი პრეზენტაციის მართვის გზების დამატება ძალიან ადვილია. Calligra-სთან ინტეგრაციის გამო ყველაფერი, რაც Calligra-ს სხვა ელემენტებს აქვთ, Stage-შიც შეგიძლიათ, გამოიყენოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Calligra Stage“ ir viegli lietojama un vienlaicīgi daudzfunkcionāla prezentāciju programma. Ar to varat viegli veidot prezentācijas ar plašu un dažādu elementu klāstu — no grafikas līdz tekstam un no diagrammām līdz attēliem. „Calligra Stage“ varat paplašināt ar spraudņu sistēmu, kas atvieglo jaunu efektu, satura elementu vai pat prezentāciju pārvaldīšanas veidu pievienošanu. Tā kā „Stage“ ir integrēta „Calligra“ programmatūrā, tad tā satur visus jaudīgos un pielāgojamos „Calligra“ satura elementus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Calligra Stage is een gemakkelijk te gebruiken maar toch flexibele toepassing voor presentaties. U kunt gemakkelijk presentaties maken met een rijke variatie van elementen, van grafische tot tekst, van grafieken tot afbeeldingen. Calligra Stage is uit te breiden met een systeem van plug-ins, zodat het gemakkelijk is om nieuwe effecten toe te voegen, nieuwe soorten inhoud of zelfs nieuwe manieren van het beheren van uw presentatie. Vanwege de integratie met Calligra, is alle kracht en flexibiliteit van de inhoudselementen van Calligra beschikbaar in Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Scena Calligra jest łatwym w użyciu, a zarazem elastycznym programem do prezentowania. Można łatwo tworzyć prezentację zawierające bogatą różnorodność elementów, od grafiki do tekstu, od wykresów do obrazów. Scena Calligra jest rozszerzalna przez system wtyczek, tak że można łatwo dodać nowe efekty, nowe elementy lub nawet nowe sposoby na zarządzanie prezentacją. Ze względów na powiązanie z Calligrą, cała moc i elastyczność elementów Calligry jest dostępna również dla Sceny.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Calligra Stage je enostavna za uporabo in prilagodljiva aplikacija za predstavitve  Z lahkoto lahko ustvarite predstavitve, ki vsebujejo bogato paletoelementov, od grafik do besedila, od grafikonov do slik. Calligra Stage jerazširljiv prek sistema vtičnikov, tako da je preprosto dodajanje novih učinkov, novihelementov vsebine ali celo nove načine upravljanja predstavitev v Stageu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Calligra Stage är ett lättanvänt men ändå flexibelt presentationsprogram. Du kan enkelt skapa presentationer som innehåller en mängd olika element, från grafik till text, från diagram till bilder. Calligra Stage är utbyggbart genom ett insticksprogramsystem, så det är enkelt att lägga till nya effekter, nya innehållselement eller till och med nya sätt att hantera en presentation. På grund av integrationen med Calligra är all kraft och flexibilitet i Calligras innehållselementen tillgängliga i Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Calligra Sahne, kullanımı kolay; ancak yine de esnek bir sunum uygulamasıdır. Grafiklerden metne, çizelgelerden resimlere kadar zengin çeşitlilikte öğeler içeren sunumları kolayca oluşturabilirsiniz. Calligra Sahne, bir eklenti sistemi aracılığıyla genişletilebilir, bu nedenle yeni efektler, yeni içerik ögeleri veya hatta sunumunuzu yönetmenin yeni yollarını eklemek kolaydır. Calligra ile tümleşim sayesinde, Calligra içerik ögelerinin tüm gücü ve esnekliği Sahne’ye sunulur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Calligra Stage — проста, але потужна програма для роботи з презентаціями. За її допомогою ви без проблем зможете створити презентацію з багатим набором елементів, від графіки до тексту, від діаграм до зображень. Можливості Calligra Stage можна розширити за допомогою системи додатків: ви можете додати нові ефекти, нові елементи вмісту і навіть нові способи керування презентацією. Через тісну інтеграцію з рештою програм Calligra ви можете скористатися усіма потужними та гнучкими елементами решти програм Calligra безпосередньо у Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application. You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system, so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.xx</p>
    <!-- Karbon -->
    <p>
      Karbon is a vector drawing application with a user interface that is easy to use, highly customizable and extensible.
      That makes Karbon a great application for users starting to explore the world of vector graphics as well as for artists
      wanting to create breathtaking vector art.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Karbon és una aplicació de dibuix vectorial amb una interfície d'usuari senzilla d'utilitzar, que es pot personalitzar i ampliar molt. Això converteix el Karbon en una gran aplicació per a usuaris que comencin a explorar el món dels gràfics vectorials i també pels artistes que volen crear art vectorial que deixi bocabadat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Karbon és una aplicació de dibuix vectorial amb una interfície d'usuari senzilla d'utilitzar, la qual es pot personalitzar i ampliar molt. Açò convertix Karbon en una gran aplicació per a usuaris que comencen a explorar el món dels gràfics vectorials i també pels artistes que volen crear art vectorial que deixe bocabadat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Karbon es una aplicación de dibujo vectorial con una interfaz de usuario fácil de usar, altamente personalizable y extensible. Esto hace que Karbon sea una gran aplicación para los usuarios que empiezan a explorar el mundo de los gráficos vectoriales así como para los artistas que quieren crear composiciones vectoriales sorprendentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Karbon, marrazketa bektorialeko aplikazio bat da, erabiltzen erraza den erabiltzaile-interfaze bat, norbere gustura oso egokigarria, duena. Hori dela eta, Karbon bikaina da grafiko bektorialen mundua esploratzen hasitako erabiltzaileentzat, baita arte bektorial txundigarriak sortu nahi dituzten artistentzat ere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Karbon é unha aplicación de debuxo vectorial cunha interface de usuario fácil de usar, personalizar e ampliar. Iso fai de Karbon unha gran aplicación para usuarios que comezan a explorar o mundo das imaxes vectoriais, pero tamén para artistas que queren crear impresionantes obras de arte vectoriais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Karbon הוא יישום לציור וקטורי עם ממשק משתמש קל לשימוש, גמיש וניתן להרחבה. כל אלו הופכים את Karbon ליישום מעולה למשתמשים שמתחילים לחקור את עולם הגרפיקה הווקטורית לרבות אומנים שרוצים ליצור אומנות וקטורית עוצרת נשימה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Karbon è un'applicazione di disegno vettoriale con un'interfaccia utente facile da utilizzare, altamente personalizzabile ed estensibile. Ciò rende Karbon un'ottima applicazione per gli utenti che iniziano a esplorare il mondo della grafica vettoriale e per gli artisti che desiderano creare arte vettoriale mozzafiato.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Karbon ვექტორული ხაზვის აპლიკაციაა მომხმარებლის ინტერფეისით რომელიც იოლი, მორგებადი და გაფართოებადია. ეს Karbon-ს გადასარევ აპლიკაციად ქმნის მოხმარებლებისთვის, რომლებსაც სურთ, მიმოიხილონ ვექტორული გრაფიკის სამყარო და ხელოვნებისთვის, რომლებიც სუნთქვისშემკვრელ ვექტორულ გრაფიკას ქმნიან.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Karbon“ ir vektoru zīmēšanas programma ar viegli lietojamu, pielāgojamu un paplašināmu lietotāja saskarni. Tas „Karbon“ padara par lielisku programmu lietotājiem, kuri tikai sāk izpētīt vektoru grafiku pasauli, kā arī māksliniekiem, kuri vēlas radīt elpu aizraujošu mākslu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Karbon is een toepassing voor tekenen met vectoren met een gebruikersinterface dat gemakkelijk is te gebruiken, zeer goed aan te passen en uit te breiden. Dit maakt Karbon een geweldige toepassing voor gebruikers die de wereld van grafiek met vectoren aan het verkennen zijn evenals voor kunstenaars die adembenemende vectorkunst willen maken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Karbon jest programem do rysowania wektorowego z układem sterowania, który jest łatwy w użyciu, wysoce dostosowywalny i rozszerzalny. To czyni Karbon wspaniałym programem dla użytkowników zaczynających poznawanie świata grafiki wektorowej, a artystów zachęca do tworzenie sztuki wektorowej zapierającej dech w piersiach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Karbon je aplikacija za vektorsko risanje z uporabniškim vmesnikom, ki je preprosta za uporabo, zelo prilagodljiva in razširljiva. Zaradi tega je Karbon odlična aplikacija za uporabnike, ki začenjajo raziskovati svet vektorske grafike kotkot tudi za umetnike, ki želijo ustvariti osupljivo vektorsko umetnost.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Karbon är ett vektorritprogram med ett användargränssnitt som är lätt att använda, ytterst anpassningsbart och utökningsbart. Det gör Karbon till ett utmärkt program för användare som börjar utforska vektorgrafikvärlden samt för konstnärer som vill skapa hänförande vektorkonst.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Karbon, kullanımı kolay, son derece özelleştirilebilir ve genişletilebilir bir kullanıcı arayüzüne sahip bir vektör çizim uygulamasıdır. Bu, Karbon’u vektör grafikleri dünyasını keşfetmeye başlayan kullanıcılar ve nefes kesici vektör sanatı yaratmak isteyen sanatçılar için harika bir uygulama haline getirir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Karbon — програма для векторного малювання з простим, гнучким та придатним до розширення інтерфейсом користувача. Це робить Karbon чудовою програмою для користувачів, які починають знайомитися зі світом векторної графіки, а також для художників, які хочуть створити захопливі векторні твори.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKarbon is a vector drawing application with a user interface that is easy to use, highly customizable and extensible. That makes Karbon a great application for users starting to explore the world of vector graphics as well as for artists wanting to create breathtaking vector art.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.calligra.org/words/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=calligrawords</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calligra/words-desktop-mode.png</image>
      <caption>Calligra Words main window showing random text in the main editor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del Words del Calligra que mostra text aleatori a l'editor principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Words de Calligra que mostra text aleatori a l'editor principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de Calligra Words que muestra un texto aleatorio en el editor principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Calligra Words-en leiho nagusia editore nagusian hausazko testua erakutsiz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xanela principal de Calligra Words amosando texto aleatorio no editor principal.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי של Calligra מילים שמציג טקסט אקראי בעורך הראשי</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale di Calligra Words che mostra testo casuale nell'editor principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Calligra Words-ის მთავარი ფანჯარა შემთხვევითი ტექსტით რედაქტორში</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">„Calligra Words“ pamata logs ar tekstu galvenajā teksta laukā</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Calligra Words die willekeurige tekst in de hoofdbewerker toont</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Słów Calligry, pokazujące losowy tekst w głównym edytorze</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno Calligra Words, ki prikazuje naključno besedilo v glavnem urejevalniku</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Calligra Words huvudfönster som visar slumpmässig text i huvudeditorn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ana düzenleyicide rastgele bir metin parçası gösteren Calligra Sözcükler ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Calligra Words із випадковим текстом у основному редакторі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Words main window showing random text in the main editorxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calligrasheets/calligrasheets.png</image>
      <caption>Calligra Sheets main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del Sheets del Calligra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Sheets de Calligra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de Calligra Sheets</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Calligra Sheets leiho nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xanela principal de Calligra Sheets.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי של Calligra גיליונות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale di Calligra Sheets</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Calligra Sheets-ის მთავარი ფანჯარა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">„Calligra Sheets“ pamata logs</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Calligra Sheets</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Arkuszy Calligry</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno Calligra Sheets</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Calligra Sheets huvudfönster</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Calligra Tablolar ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Calligra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Sheets main windowxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calligra/calligrastage.png</image>
      <caption>Calligra Stage main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del Stage del Calligra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Stage de Calligra</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de Calligra Stage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Calligra Stage leiho nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xanela principal de Calligra Stage.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי של Calligra במה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale di Calligra Stage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Calligra Stage-ის მთავარი ფანჯარა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">„Calligra Stage“ pamata logs</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Calligra Stage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Sceny Calligry</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno Calligra Stage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Calligra Stage huvudfönster</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Calligra Sahne ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Calligra Stage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Stage main windowxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://carlschwan.eu/2024/08/27/calligra-office-4.0-is-out/karbon.png</image>
      <caption>Main window of Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Karbon-en leiho nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xanela principal de Karbon.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי של Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">La finestra principale di Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Karbon-ის მთავარი ფანჯარა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">„Karbon“ pamata logs</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Karbona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönstret i Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Karbon ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Karbon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain window of Karbonxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#f5aa33</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#694917</color>
  </branding>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.calligra.desktop</launchable>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name>The KDE Community</name>
    <url>https://kde.org</url>
  </developer>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.0.1" date="2024-09-03">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2024/09/02/calligra-office-4.0.1/</url>
      <description>
        <p>This release add flatpak support to the Calligra Office suite.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2024-08-27">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2024/08/27/calligra-office-4.0-is-out/</url>
      <description>
        <p>The most significant changes are that Calligra has been fully transitioned to Qt6 and KF6, along with a major overhaul of its user interface.</p>
        <p>Words, Sheets, and Stage now feature a new sidebar design. The “Custom Shape” docker has been removed, and custom shapes are now accessible through a popup menu in the toolbar across all Calligra applications. We simplified the toolbar and removed the basic copy, paste and cut actions.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
