<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.calligra.braindump</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.calligra.braindump.desktop</launchable>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name>The KDE Community</name>
    <url>https://kde.org</url>
  </developer>
  <name>Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">סיעור מוחין</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">브레인덤프</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">BrainDump</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Braindump</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBraindumpxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Braindump</name>
  <summary>Notes and ideas gathering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Sakupljanje poruka i ideja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Notes i recull d'idees</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Notes i arreplega d'idees</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Shromažďování nápadů poznámek</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Notizen und Ideen sammeln</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Συλλογή σημειώσεων και ιδεών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Notes and ideas gathering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Kolektado de notoj kaj ideoj</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Recopilación de notas e ideas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Märkmed ja ideede kogumine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Oharrak eta ideiak biltzea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Muistiinpanot ja ideointi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Notes et ensemble d'idées</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Recolección de notas e ideas.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">איסוף הערות ורעיונות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Penghasil gagasan dan catatan</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Note e raccolta di idee</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">შენიშვნების და იდეების შეგროვება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">메모 및 아이디어 수집</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Piezīmju un ideju vākšana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Notities en ideeën verzamelen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zbieranie uwag i pomysłów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Recolha de notas e ideias</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Juntando notas e ideias</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Программа для хранения заметок и идей</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zbieranie poznámok a nápadov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Zbiranje zapiskov in idej</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Anteckningar och idéinsamling</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Notları ve fikirleri toplama</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для впорядковування нотаток та ідей</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxNotes and ideas gatheringxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">笔记和思路速记工具</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Braindump is a tool to dump and organize the content of your brain (ideas, drawings, images, texts…) to your computer.
      It works by allowing to create and edit whiteboards, which are infinite canvas on which you can add texts, images, charts, drawings, etc.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Braindump je alat za slanje i organizaciju sadržaja vašeg mozga (ideja, crteža, slika, teksta...) na računar. Radi tako što vam dopušta da kreirate i uređujete table koja su beskonačna platna na koje možete dodati tekstove, slike, dijagrame, crteže itd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Braindump és una eina per a bolcar i organitzar el contingut del cervell (idees, dibuixos, imatges, texts…) a l'ordinador. Funciona permetent crear i editar pissarres, que tenen llenços infinits en els quals es pot afegir texts, imatges, diagrames, dibuixos, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Braindump és una eina per a bolcar i organitzar el contingut del cervell (idees, dibuixos, imatges, texts…) a l'ordinador. Funciona permetent crear i editar pissarres, que tenen llenços infinits en els quals es pot afegir texts, imatges, diagrames, dibuixos, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Braindump είναι ένα εργαλείο αποθήκευσης και οργάνωσης του περιεχομένου του εγκεφάλου σου (ιδέες, σχήματα, εικόνες, κείμενα…) στον υπολογιστή σου. Λειτουργεί με το να επιτρέπει τη δημιουργία και την επεξεργασία λευκοπινάκων, οι οποίοι αποτελούν έναν απεριόριστο καμβά για την προσθήκη κειμένων, εικόνων, διαγραμμάτων, σχημάτων, κλπ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Braindump is a tool to dump and organise the content of your brain (ideas, drawings, images, texts…) to your computer. It works by allowing to create and edit whiteboards, which are infinite canvas on which you can add texts, images, charts, drawings, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Braindump estas ilo por ŝuti kaj organizi la enhavon de via cerbo (ideoj, desegnaĵoj, bildoj, tekstoj…) al via komputilo. Ĝi funkcias permesante krei kaj redakti blanktabulojn, kiuj estas senfinaj kanvasoj, sur kiuj vi povas aldoni tekstojn, bildojn, diagramojn, desegnaĵojn ktp.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Braindump es una herramienta para volcar y organizar el contenido de su cerebro (ideas, dibujos, imágenes, texto...) en su equipo. Permite crear y editar pizarras en blanco, es decir, lienzos infinitos en los que puede añadir textos, imágenes, diagramas, dibujos, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Braindump on tööriist sinu ajus peituva sisu (mõtted, joonised, pildid, tekst jms) esitamiseks ja korraldamiseks arvutis. See võimaldab luua ja muuta nõndanimetatud valgetahvleid, mis kujutavad endast piiramata lõuendeid, kuhu lisada teksti, pilte, skeeme, diagramme, joonistusi ja kõike muud vajalikku.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Braindump, zure buruan darabilzuna (ideiak, marrazkiak, irudiak, testuak…) zure ordenagailura eraman eta antolatzeko tresna bat da. Arbel zuriak sortu eta editatzeko aukera ematen du, testuak, irudiak, diagramak, eta abar gehitu ditzakezun oihal infinituak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Braindump on työkalu aivojesi sisällön (ajatusten, piirrosten, kuvien, tekstin…) purkamiseksi ja järjestämiseksi. Se toimii antamalla sinun luoda ja muokata valkotauluja, jotka ovat rajaton kangas tekstillesi, kuvillesi, kaavioillesi, piirroksillesi jne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Braindump est un outil pour mettre en ordre le contenu de votre cerveau (idées, dessins, images, textes…) sur votre ordinateur. Il vous permet de créer et d'éditer des tableaux blancs illimités sur lesquels vous pouvez ajouter des textes, des images, des graphiques, des dessins, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Braindump é unha ferramenta para envorcar e organizar o que pasa pola súa cabeza (ideas, debuxos, imaxes, textos…) no seu computador. Permítelle crear e editar encerados, que son lenzos infinitos nos que pode engadir textos, imaxes, gráficos, debuxos…</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">סיעור מוחין הוא כלי לתיעוד וסידור תוכן המוח שלך (רעיונות, ציורים, תמונות, טקסטים…) למחשב שלך. הוא עובד דרך הרשאה ליצירת ועריכת לוחות תכנון, שהן משטחי ציור אינסופיים שאפשר להוסיף להם טקסטים, תמונות, תרשימים, ציורים ועוד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Braindump es un instrumento pro discargar e organizar le contento de tu cerebro (ideas, designos, imagines, textos...) in tu computator. Illo functiona per permitter crear e modificar tabula blanc, que es telas infinite sur le qual on pote adder textos, imagines, diagrammas, designos, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Braindump adalah alat untuk membuang dan mengorganisir konten pikiran Anda (gagasan, gambar, citra, teks ...) ke komputer Anda. Ini bekerja dengan membolehkankan untuk menciptakan dan mengedit papan tulis, yang merupakan kanvas tanpa batas di mana kamu bisa menambahkan teks, gambar, grafik, citra, dll.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Braindump è uno strumento per estrarre e organizzare il contenuto del tuo cervello (idee, disegni, immagini, testi...) sul tuo computer. Ti consente di creare e modificare lavagne bianche, che sono tele infinite sulle quali puoi aggiungere testi, immagini, grafici, disegni, ecc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Braindump ხელსაწყოა თქვენი ტვინიდან იდეების (იდეები, ნახაზები, სურათები, ტექსტები) კომპიუტერში მოსაგროვებლად. ის მუშაობს დაფების შექმნის და ჩასწორების საშუალებიც, რაც უსასრულო ტილოს წარმოადგენს, სადაც ტექსტის, სურათების, გრაფიკების, ნახატების და ა.შ. დალაგება შეგიძლიათ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">브레인덤프는 두뇌의 내용(아이디어, 그림, 이미지, 텍스트 등)을 컴퓨터에 떠넘기고 정리하는 도구입니다. 텍스트, 이미지, 차트, 그림 등을 추가할 수 있는 무한 캔버스인 화이트 보드를 만들고 편집할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Braindump“ ir rīks, kas ir paredzēts prāta satura (ideju, skiču, attēlu, teksta...) nomešanai datorā. Tas ļauj veidot un rediģēt bezgalīgas tāfeles, uz kurām varat novietot tekstus, attēlus, diagrammas, zīmējumu utt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Braindump is een hulpmiddel om de inhoud van uw brein te dumpen en te organiseren (ideeën, tekeningen, afbeeldingen, teksten…) naar uw computer. Het werkt door u instaat te stellen whiteboards te bewerken, die oneindige werkvelden zijn waarop u teksten, afbeeldingen, grafieken, tekeningen, etc. kunt toevoegen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Braindump jest narzędziem do zrzucania i porządkowania zawartości twojego umysłu (pomysły, rysunki, obrazy, teksty...) na komputer. Działa przez umożliwianie tworzenia i edytowania białych tablic, które są bezgranicznym płótnem, na które można dodawać teksty, obrazy, wykresy, rysunki, itp.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Braindump é uma ferramenta para descarregar e organizar o conteúdo do seu cérebro (ideias, desenhos, imagens, textos, ...) para o seu computador. Permite criar e editar quadros, que são uma "tela" infinita onde poderá adicionar textos, imagens, gráficos, desenhos, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Braindump é uma ferramenta para descarregar e organizar o conteúdo do seu cérebro (ideias, desenhos, imagens, textos, ...) para o seu computador. Permite-lhe criar e editar quadros, que são uma espécie de "tela infinita" onde poderá adicionar textos, imagens, gráficos, desenhos, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Braindump je nástroj na prenos a organizáciu obsahu vášho mozgu (nápady, kresby, obrázky, texty...) do vášho počítača. Umožňuje vytvárať a upravovať tabule, ktoré sú neurčitým plátnom, kam môžete pridávať texty, obrázky, grafy, kresby atď.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Braindump je orodje za zajem in organiziranje vsebine vaših možganov (ideje,risbe, slike, besedila…) v računalnik. Deluje tako, da omogoča ustvarjanjein ureditev tabel, ki so neskončno platno, na katerega lahko dodate besedila,slike, grafikoni, risbe itd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Braindump är ett verktyg för att hämta och organisera innehållet i din hjärna (idéer, ritningar, bilder, texter …) på datorn. Det fungerar genom att låta dig skapa och redigera skrivtavlor, som är oändliga ytor där du kan lägga till texter, bilder, diagram, ritningar, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Braindump, aklınızdaki içerikleri (fikirler, çizimler, görseller, metinler…) bilgisayarına dökmenize ve organize etmenize yardımcı olan bir araçtır. Metin, görsel, çizelge, çizimler, vb. ekleyebileceğiniz sonsuz tuval olan beyaz tahtalar oluşturup düzenlemenize izin vererek çalışır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Braindump — програма для запису та упорядкування ваших думок (ідей, креслень, зображень, фрагментів тексту…) за допомогою вашого комп’ютера. У цій програмі ви можете створювати та редагувати так звані «дошки» — нескінченні полотна, на які можна додавати фрагменти тексту, зображення, діаграми, креслення тощо.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxBraindump is a tool to dump and organize the content of your brain (ideas, drawings, images, texts…) to your computer. It works by allowing to create and edit whiteboards, which are infinite canvas on which you can add texts, images, charts, drawings, etc.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Braindump 是一款用于快速记录和组织思路和信息的工具。您可以创建和编辑白板，在无限大小的画布中随意添加文字、图像、图表、绘图等。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://calligra.org/braindump/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=braindump</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/calligra/braindump.png</image>
      <caption>Main window of Braindump showing a music partition and many other shapes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Finestra principal del Braindump que mostra una partitura musical i moltes altres formes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Finestra principal de Braindump que mostra una partitura musical i moltes altres formes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Ventana principal de Braindump que muestra una partitura musical y otras formas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Braindump-en leiho nagusia musika partizio bat eta beste forma asko erakusten duena</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Fenêtre principale de Braindump affichant une partition musicale et de nombreuses autres formes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xanela principal de Braindump amosando unha división musical e moitas outras formas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי של סיעור מוחין שמציג חלק מוזיקלי ושלל צורות נוספות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Finestra principale di Braindump che mostra una partitura musicale e molte altre forme</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">Braindump-ის მთავარი ფანჯარა, რომელიც მუსიკის დანაყოფს და ბევრ სხვა ფიგურას აჩვენებს</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">„Brandump“ galvenais logs ar nošu pierakstu un citiem objektiem.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdvenster van Braindump die een muziekpartitie en vele andere vormen toont</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Braindump, pokazujące partyturę muzyczną i wiele innych kształtów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno Braindumpa, ki prikazuje glasbeno particijo in številne druge oblike</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudfönster i Braindump som visar en musikpartition och många andra former</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Braindump’ın bir müzik partisyonu ve birçok başka şekli gösteren ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно Braindump із показаною музичною партитурою та багатьма іншими формами</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain window of Braindump showing a music partition and many other shapesxx</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#ffd28f</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#643a00</color>
  </branding>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#calligra:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>braindump</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.0.1" date="2024-09-03">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2024/09/02/calligra-office-4.0.1/</url>
      <description>
        <p>This release add flatpak support to the Calligra Office suite.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2024-08-27">
      <url>https://carlschwan.eu/2024/08/27/calligra-office-4.0-is-out/</url>
      <description>
        <p>The most significant changes are that Calligra has been fully transitioned to Qt6 and KF6, along with a major overhaul of its user interface.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
