<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kexi.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKexixx</name>
  <summary>Database Creator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Generador de bases de dades</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Tvůrce databází</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Creator de base de datos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Creazione di basi di dati</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Database aanmaken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie baz danych</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Criador de Bases de Dados</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de bancos de dados</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správa databázy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Databasskapare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для створення баз даних</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDatabase Creatorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kexi is a visual database creator, part of the Calligra Suite.
      It can be used for designing database applications, inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data.
      Forms can be created to provide a custom interface to your data.
      All database objects - tables, queries, forms, reports - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kexi és un generador visual de base de dades, part del paquet ofimàtic Calligra. Es pot utilitzar per dissenyar aplicacions de bases de dades, inserció i edició de dades, execució de consultes, i procés de dades. Es poden generar formularis per proporcionar una interfície personalitzada a les dades. Tots els objecte de les bases de dades -taules, consultes, formularis, informes- s'emmagatzemen en la base de dades, facilitant compartir les dades i el disseny.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kexi è uno strumento visuale per la creaazione di basi di dati, parte di Calligra Suite. Può essere utilizzato per progettare applicazioni che usano basi di dati, inserire e modificare dati, eseguire query ed elaborare dati. Puoi creare moduli per fornire un'interfaccia personalizzata ai tuoi dati. Tutti gli oggetti di una base di dati - tabelle, query, moduli, report - sono memorizzati nella base di dati stessa, semplificando la condivisione dei dati e la progettazione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kexi is een maakprogramma van een database op een visuele manier, onderdeel van de Calligra Suite. Het kan gebruikt worden voor het ontwerpen van toepassingen met een database, gegevens invoeren en bewerken, zoekopdrachten uitvoeren en gegevens verwerken. Formulieren kunnen gemaakt worden om een aangepast interface naar uw gegevens te bieden. Alle database-objecten - tabellen, zoekopdrachten, formulieren, rapporten - worden opgeslagen in de database, waarmee het gemakkelijk wordt gegevens en ontwerp te delen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kexi jest programem do wizualnego tworzenia bazy danych, jest częścią Pakietu Calligra. Można go używać do opracowywania programów baz danych, wstawiania i edytowania danych, wykonywania zapytań i do przetwarzania danych. Istnieje możliwość tworzenia formularzy do zapewnienia własnego układu sterowania dl twoich danych. Wszystkie obiekty baz danych - tabele, zapytania, formularze, sprawozdania - są przechowywane w bazie danych, czyniąc je łatwiejszymi przy współdzieleniu i opracowywaniu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kexi é um criador de bases de dados visuais, que faz parte do pacote Calligra. Pode ser usado para desenhar aplicações de bases de dados, inserir e editar dados, executar pesquisas e processar os dados. Poderá criar formulários para oferecer uma interface personalizada para os seus dados. Todos os objectos da base de dados - tabelas, pesquisas, formulários, relatórios - são guardados na base de dados, tornando simples a partilha e o desenho dos dados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Kexi é um criador visual de banco de dados, integrante do pacote Calligra. Pode ser usado para desenhar aplicativos de banco de dados, inserir e editar dados, executar pesquisas e processar dados. Podem ser criados formulários para oferecer uma interface personalizada para seus dados. Todos os objetos do banco de dados - tabelas, pesquisas, formulários, relatórios - são armazenados no próprio banco de dados, tornando simples o compartilhamento de dados e o visual.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kexi je vizuálny tvorca databáz, súčasť Calligra Suite. Dá sa použiť na návrh databázových aplikácií, vkladanie a úpravu údajov, vykonávanie dotazov a spracúvanie údajov. Formuláre sa dajú vytvoriť na poskytnutie vlastného rozhrania pre vaše údaje. Všetky databázové objekty - tabuľky, dotazy, formuláre, správy - sú uložené v databáze, čo uľahčuje zdieľanie dát a dizajn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kexi är en visuell databasskapare, en del av Calligra-sviten. Den kan användas för att skapa databasprogram, infoga och redigera data, ställa frågor och behandla data. Formulär kan skapas för att tillhandahålla ett anpassat gränssnitt för data. Alla databasobjekt (tabeller, frågor, formulär, rapporter) lagras i databasen, vilket gör det enkelt att dela data och konstruktion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kexi — програма для створення баз даних у візуальному режимі, частина комплексу програм Calligra. Цією програмою можна скористатися для створень мініпрограм для роботи з базами даних, додавання та редагування даних, виконання запитів та обробки даних. За допомогою створених програмою форм ви можете отримати потрібний вам режим доступу до ваших даних. Всі об’єкти баз даних — таблиці, запити, форми, звіти, — зберігаються у самій базі даних, що спрощує поширення даних та представлення даних.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKexi is a visual database creator, part of the Calligra Suite. It can be used for designing database applications, inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data. Forms can be created to provide a custom interface to your data. All database objects - tables, queries, forms, reports - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Full visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reports</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Dissenyadors visuals complets per taules, consultes, formularis i informes</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Progettazione completamente visuale di tabelle, query e report</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Volledige visueel ontwerpen van tabellen, zoekopdrachten, formulieren en rapporten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">W pełni wizualna możliwość tworzenia tabel, zapytań, formularzy i sprawozdań</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenhadores visuais completos para tabelas, pesquisas, formulários e relatórios</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Desenhos visuais completos para tabelas, pesquisas, formulários e relatórios</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Plne vizuálny návrh pre tabuľky, dotazy, formuláre a správy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständigt visuell konstruktion av tabeller, frågor, formulär och rapporter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повноцінне візуальне середовище для створення таблиць, запитів, форм та звітів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reportsxx</li>
      <li>Running queries, support for parametrized queries</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Execució de consultes, implementació de consultes paramètriques</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Esecuzione di query, supporto per le query parametriche</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Zoekopdrachten uitvoeren, ondersteuning voor zoekopdrachten met parameters</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wykonywanie zapytań, obsługa dla zapytań parametrycznych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Execução de pesquisas, suporte para pesquisas parametrizadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Execução de pesquisas, suporte para pesquisas parametrizadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Spúšťanie dotazov, podpora pre parametrizované dotazy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ställa frågor, stöd för parameterbaserade frågor</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконання запитів, підтримка параметризованих запитів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxRunning queries, support for parametrized queriesxx</li>
      <li>Supports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL and MS SQL Server databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet bases de dades SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL i MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta le basi di dati SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL e MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt databases SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL en MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL oraz baz danych MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta bases de dados SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL e MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte aos banco de dados SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL e MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje databázy SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL a MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder databaserna SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL och MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка баз даних SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL та MS SQL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL and MS SQL Server databasesxx</li>
      <li>The only multiplatform graphical tool importing data from MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">L'única eina gràfica multiplataforma d'importació de dades des de les bases de dades MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Il solo strumento grafico multipiattaforma in grado di importare basi di dati MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Het enige multiplatform grafische hulpmiddel die gegevens importeert uit MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Jedyne graficzne narzędzie wieloplatformowe importujące dane z baz danych MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A única ferramenta gráfica multi-plataforma que consegue importar bases de dados MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Única ferramenta gráfica multiplataforma que consegue importar banco de dados do MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Jediný mnohoplatformový grafický nástroj importujúci údaje z databáz MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Det enda grafiska verktyget för flera plattformar som importerar data från MS Access-databaser</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Єдиний графічний багатоплатформовий інструмент, здатний імпортувати дані з баз даних MS Access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThe only multiplatform graphical tool importing data from MS Access databasesxx</li>
      <li>Supports query design in dedicated SQL view</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet el disseny de consultes en vistes SQL dedicades</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta la progettazione di query in una vista SQL dedicata</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt ontwerp van zoekopdrachten in een gerichte SQL-weergave</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje zapytania w widoku przeznaczonym dla SQL</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta o desenho de pesquisas numa área de SQL dedicada</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para desenho de pesquisas em uma área de SQL dedicada</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje návrh dotazov vo vyhradenom SQL pohľade</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder frågekonstruktion i en dedicerad SQL-vy</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка створення запитів за допомогою спеціальної панелі SQL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports query design in dedicated SQL viewxx</li>
      <li>Designing and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Disseny i visualització de dades relacionals usant quadres combinats (columnes de cerca)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Progettazione e visualizzazione dei dati relazionali utilizzando caselle combinate (colonne di ricerca)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ontwerpen en tonen van relationele gegevens met gebruik van keuzelijsten (kolommen voor opzoeken)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Opracowywanie i wyświetlanie danych relacyjnych przy użyciu pól rozwijanych (kolumn wyszukiwania)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenho e apresentação de dados relacionais com listas (colunas de pesquisa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Desenho e apresentação de dados relacionais usando listas (colunas de pesquisa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Návrh a zobrazenie relačných dát pomocou combo boxov (lookup stĺpce)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Konstruktion och visning av relationsdata med användning av kombinationsrutor (uppslagning av kolumner)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення та показ пов’язаних даних за допомогою спадних списків (стовпчики пошуку).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDesigning and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)xx</li>
      <li>Direct data entry or import using CSV format</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Entrada directa de dades o importació usant el format CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Inserimento diretto dei dati o importazione utilizzando il formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Directe invoer van gegevens of importeren met het CSV-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Bezpośrednie wprowadzanie danych lub importowanie ich z postaci CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Introdução ou importação directa de dados com o formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Entrada ou importação direta de dados usando o formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Priamy vstup údajov alebo import pomocou formátu CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Direkt datainmatning eller import med CSV-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Безпосереднє введення даних або імпортування даних у форматі CSV.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDirect data entry or import using CSV formatxx</li>
      <li>Locked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's design</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mode reduït d'usuari, que permet deshabilitar totes les ordres relacionades amb l'edició del disseny del projecte</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Modalità utente bloccata, che ti consente di disattivare tutti i comandi in grado di modificare la struttura del tuo progetto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Vergrendelde gebruikersodus, waarmee u alle commando's uitschakelt die zijn gerelateerd aan bewerken en ontwerpen van uw project</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zamknięty tryb użytkownika, umożliwiający wyłączenie wszystkich poleceń związanych z edytowaniem twojego projektu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Modo reduzido de utilizador, permitindo-lhe desligar todos os comandos relacionados com a edição do desenho do seu projecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modo de usuário reduzido, permitindo-lhe desligar todos os comandos relacionados à edição do visual do seu projeto</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Uzamknutý používateľský režim, umožňujúci vám vypnúť všetky príkazy súvisiace s úpravou dizajnu vášho projektu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Låsbart användarläge, som låter dig stänga av alla kommandon relaterade till redigering av projektets konstruktion</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Заблокований режим користувача, у якому можна вимкнути усі пов’язані з командами редагування компонування вашого проекту команди.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLocked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's designxx</li>
      <li>Scripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Crear scripts usant els llenguatges de programació JavaScript, Python o Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Creazione script utilizzando i linguaggi di programmazione JavaScript, Python o Ruby (sperimentale)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Scripting met de programmeertalen JavaScript, Python of Ruby (experimenteel)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Skrypty wykorzystujące języki programowania JavaScript, Python lub Ruby (eksperymentalnie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Programável através das linguagens JavaScript, Python ou Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de scripts usando as linguagens de programação JavaScript, Python ou Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Skriptovanie pomocou programovacích jazykov JavaScript, Python alebo Ruby (experimentálne)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skript med användning av programspråken Javascript, Python eller Ruby (experimentellt)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Керування за допомогою скриптів мовами JavaScript, Python та Ruby (експериментальна можливість).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.calligra.org/kexi/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kexi</url>
  <url type="help">http://userbase.kde.org/Kexi/Handbook</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kexi.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Table View storing images</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de taula emmagatzemant imatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista tabella per archiviare immagini</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Tabelweergave bij opslaan van afbeeldingen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Przechowywanie obrazów w widoku tabeli</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A área da tabela permite guardar as imagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Área da tabela armazenando imagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Tabuľkový pohľad uloženia obrázkov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tabellvy som lagrar bilder</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Збереження зображень у перегляді таблиць.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTable View storing imagesxx</caption>
      <image>http://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/kexi-2.2-rc1-tableview-images.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Form Designer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Dissenyador de formularis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Progettazione moduli</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Ontwerper van formulieren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Opracowywanie formularzy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Desenhador de Formulários</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta de desenho de formulários</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Návrhár formulárov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Formulärkonstruktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Засіб для розробки форм.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxForm Designerxx</caption>
      <image>http://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/kexi-2.3-form.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligrakexi</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
