<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kexi.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKexixx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kexi</name>
  <summary>Visual database apps builder</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Constructor visual d'aplicacions de bases de dades</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Constructor visual d'aplicacions de bases de dades</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Visual database apps builder</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Constructor visual de aplicaciones de base de datos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Visuaalinen tietokantasovellusten luonti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Constructeur d'applications de bases de données visuel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Generatore visuale di applicazioni di banche dati</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Visuele database van bouwer van apps</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Construtor visual de aplicações de bases de dados</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Construtor visual de aplicativos de banco de dados</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vizuálny tvorca databázových aplikácií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visuellt byggverktyg för databasprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для побудови візуальних обробників баз даних</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxVisual database apps builderxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kexi is a visual database applications builder. It can be used for designing database applications,
      inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data. Forms can be created
      to provide a custom interface to your data. All database objects - tables, queries, forms,
      reports, etc. - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kexi és un constructor visual de base de dades. Es pot utilitzar per dissenyar aplicacions de bases de dades, inserció i edició de dades, execució de consultes, i procés de dades. Es poden generar formularis per proporcionar una interfície personalitzada a les dades. Tots els objectes de les bases de dades -taules, consultes, formularis, informes, etc.- s'emmagatzemen en la base de dades, facilitant compartir les dades i el disseny.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Kexi és un constructor visual de base de dades. Es pot utilitzar per dissenyar aplicacions de bases de dades, inserció i edició de dades, execució de consultes, i procés de dades. Es poden generar formularis per proporcionar una interfície personalitzada a les dades. Tots els objectes de les bases de dades -taules, consultes, formularis, informes, etc.- s'emmagatzemen en la base de dades, facilitant compartir les dades i el disseny.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kexi is a visual database applications builder. It can be used for designing database applications, inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data. Forms can be created to provide a custom interface to your data. All database objects - tables, queries, forms, reports, etc. - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kexi es un creador visual de aplicaciones de bases de datos. Se puede usar para diseñar aplicaciones de bases de datos, insertar y editar datos, realizar consultas y procesar datos. Se pueden crear formularios para proporcionar una interfaz personalizada para sus datos. Todos los objetos de la base de datos (tablas, consultas, formularios, informes, etc.) se almacenan en la base de datos, facilitando el intercambio de datos y diseños.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kexi on ohjelma tietokantasovellusten luomiseen visuaalisesti. Se on osa Calligra-ohjelmistoa. Sen avulla voi suunnitella tietokantasovelluksia, lisätä ja muokata tietoja, suorittaa kyselyjä ja käsitellä tietoja. Voit luoda lomakkeita mukauttaaksesi tietojesi käyttöliittymää. Kaikki tietokantaoliot – taulukot, kyselyt, lomakkeet, raportit jne. – tallennetaan tietokantaan, joten tiedon jako ja suunnittelu on helppoa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kexi est un constructeur d'applications de bases de données visuel. Il peut être utilisé pour concevoir des applications de base de données, insérer et éditer des données, effectuer des requêtes, et traiter des données. Des formulaires peuvent être créés pour fournir une interface personnalisée pour vos données. Tous les objets de bases de données (tables, requêtes, formulaires, rapports, etc) sont stockés dans la base de données, rendant facile le partage de données et de design.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kexi è uno strumento visuale per la creazione di banche dati. Può essere utilizzato per progettare applicazioni che usano banche dati, inserire e modificare dati, eseguire query ed elaborare dati. Puoi creare moduli per fornire un'interfaccia personalizzata ai tuoi dati. Tutti gli oggetti di una banca dati - tabelle, query, moduli, rapporti - sono memorizzati nella banca dati stessa, semplificando la condivisione dei dati e la progettazione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kexi is een bouwer van toepassingen met een database op een visuele manier. Het kan gebruikt worden voor het ontwerpen van toepassingen met een database, gegevens invoeren en bewerken, zoekopdrachten uitvoeren en gegevens verwerken. Formulieren kunnen gemaakt worden om een aangepast interface naar uw gegevens te bieden. Alle database-objecten - tabellen, zoekopdrachten, formulieren, rapporten, etc. - worden opgeslagen in de database, waarmee het gemakkelijk wordt gegevens en ontwerp te delen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kexi é um criador de bases de dados visuais, que pode ser usado para desenhar aplicações de bases de dados, inserir e editar dados, executar pesquisas e processar os dados. Poderá criar formulários para oferecer uma interface personalizada para os seus dados. Todos os objectos da base de dados - tabelas, pesquisas, formulários, relatórios, etc. - são guardados na base de dados, tornando simples a partilha e o desenho dos dados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Kexi é um construtor de aplicativos visuais de banco de dados. Pode ser usado para desenhar aplicativos de banco de dados, inserir e editar dados, executar pesquisas e processar dados. Podem ser criados formulários para oferecer uma interface personalizada para seus dados. Todos os objetos do banco de dados - tabelas, pesquisas, formulários, relatórios, etc. - são armazenados no próprio banco de dados, tornando simples o compartilhamento de dados e o visual.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kexi je vizuálny tvorca databáz, súčasť Calligra Suite. Dá sa použiť na návrh databázových aplikácií, vkladanie a úpravu údajov, vykonávanie dotazov a spracúvanie údajov. Formuláre sa dajú vytvoriť na poskytnutie vlastného rozhrania pre vaše údaje. Všetky databázové objekty - tabuľky, dotazy, formuláre, správy - sú uložené v databáze, čo uľahčuje zdieľanie dát a dizajn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kexi är ett visuell byggverktyg för databasprogram, en del av Calligra-sviten. Den kan användas för att skapa databasprogram, infoga och redigera data, ställa frågor och behandla data. Formulär kan skapas för att tillhandahålla ett anpassat gränssnitt för data. Alla databasobjekt (tabeller, frågor, formulär, rapporter, etc.) lagras i databasen, vilket gör det enkelt att dela data och konstruktion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kexi — програма для створення обробників баз даних у візуальному режимі. Цією програмою можна скористатися для створень мініпрограм для роботи з базами даних, додавання та редагування даних, виконання запитів та обробки даних. За допомогою створених програмою форм ви можете отримати потрібний вам режим доступу до ваших даних. Всі об’єкти баз даних — таблиці, запити, форми, звіти тощо, — зберігаються у самій базі даних, що спрощує поширення даних та представлення даних.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKexi is a visual database applications builder. It can be used for designing database applications, inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data. Forms can be created to provide a custom interface to your data. All database objects - tables, queries, forms, reports, etc. - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Osobine:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">機能:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Funksjoner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Full visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reports</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Potpuni vizualni dizajneri za tablice , upite , obrasce i izvještaje</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Dissenyadors visuals complets per taules, consultes, formularis i informes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Dissenyadors visuals complets per taules, consultes, formularis i informes</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Full visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reports</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Herramientas de diseño completamente visuales para las tablas, consultas, formularios e informes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Tabelite, päringute, vormide ja aruannete täielikult visuaalne kujundamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Täysin visuaalinen taulukoiden, kyselyjen, lomakkeiden ja raporttien suunnittelu</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Conception complètement visuelle pour les tables, requêtes, formulaires et rapports</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Progettazione completamente visuale di tabelle, query e report</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">テーブル、クエリー、フォームおよびレポートをすべて視覚的にでデザインできます</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Fullstendig visuell utforming for tabeller, spøøringer, skjemaer og rapporter</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Volledige visueel ontwerpen van tabellen, zoekopdrachten, formulieren en rapporten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">W pełni wizualna możliwość tworzenia tabel, zapytań, formularzy i raportów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenhadores visuais completos para tabelas, pesquisas, formulários e relatórios</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Desenhos visuais completos para tabelas, pesquisas, formulários e relatórios</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Plne vizuálny návrh pre tabuľky, dotazy, formuláre a správy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständigt visuell konstruktion av tabeller, frågor, formulär och rapporter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повноцінне візуальне середовище для створення таблиць, запитів, форм та звітів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reportsxx</li>
      <li>Running queries, support for parametrized queries</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Potrebno upite , podršku za parametrizovan upite</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Execució de consultes, implementació de consultes paramètriques</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Execució de consultes, implementació de consultes paramètriques</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ausführung von Abfragen, Unterstützung für parametrisierte Abfragen</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Running queries, support for parametrised queries</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Ejecución de consultas, soporte de consultas parametrizadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Päringute sooritamine, parameetritega päringute toetamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kyselyjen suoritus ja parametroitavien kyselyjen tuki</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Exécution de requêtes, prise en charge des requêtes paramétrées</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Esecuzione di query, supporto per le query parametriche</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">クエリーの実行、パラメータ化クエリーのサポート</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Kjøre spørriner, støtte for parametriserte spørringer</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Zoekopdrachten uitvoeren, ondersteuning voor zoekopdrachten met parameters</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wykonywanie zapytań, obsługa dla zapytań parametrycznych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Execução de pesquisas, suporte para pesquisas parametrizadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Execução de pesquisas, suporte para pesquisas parametrizadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Spúšťanie dotazov, podpora pre parametrizované dotazy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ställa frågor, stöd för parameterbaserade frågor</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконання запитів, підтримка параметризованих запитів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxRunning queries, support for parametrized queriesxx</li>
      <li>Supports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase, and Sybase/MS SQL Server databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet bases de dades SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase i Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet bases de dades SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase i Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt Datenbanken wie SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase und Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase, and Sybase/MS SQL Server databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite usar servidores de bases de datos SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase y Sybase/MS SQL</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">SQLite-, MySQL-, PostgreSQL-, xBase- ja Sybase/MS SQL Server -tietokantojen tuki</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prend en charge les bases de données SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase et Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase e banche dati Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt databases SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase en Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta bases de dados SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase e Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte aos banco de dados SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase e Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje serverové databázy SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase a Sybase/MS SQL</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder databaserna SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase och Sybase/MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка баз даних SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase та Sybase/MS SQL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL, xBase, and Sybase/MS SQL Server databasesxx</li>
      <li>The only multiplatform visual tool that can easily import data from MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">L'única eina visual multiplataforma que pot importar fàcilment dades des de les bases de dades MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'única eina visual multiplataforma que pot importar fàcilment dades des de les bases de dades MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">The only multiplatform visual tool that can easily import data from MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">La única herramienta gráfica multiplataforma que puede importar con facilidad datos de las bases de datos de MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Ainoa useampialustainen visuaalinen työkalu, jolla voi helposti tuoda tietoja MS Access -tietokannoista</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Le seul outil visuel multi plate-formes qui importe les bases de données de MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Il solo strumento grafico multipiattaforma in grado di importare facilmente da banche dati MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Het enige multiplatform visuele hulpmiddel die gemakkelijk gegevens kan importeren uit MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A única ferramenta gráfica multi-plataforma que consegue importar facilmente bases de dados MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Única ferramenta visual e multiplataforma que consegue importar facilmente um banco de dados do MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Jediný mnohoplatformový grafický nástroj importujúci údaje z databáz MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Det enda visuella verktyget för flera plattformar som enkelt kan importera data från MS Access-databaser</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Єдиний візуальний багатоплатформовий інструмент, здатний без проблем імпортувати дані з баз даних MS Access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThe only multiplatform visual tool that can easily import data from MS Access databasesxx</li>
      <li>Support for query design in dedicated SQL view</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet el disseny de consultes en vistes SQL dedicades</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet el disseny de consultes en vistes SQL dedicades</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for query design in dedicated SQL view</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite el diseño de consultas en vista SQL dedicada</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kyselyn suunnittelun tuki SQL-näkymässä</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de la conception de requêtes dans une vue SQL dédiée</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta la progettazione di query in una vista SQL dedicata</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor ontwerp van zoekopdrachten in een gerichte SQL-weergave</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta o desenho de pesquisas numa área de SQL dedicada</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para desenho de pesquisas em uma área de SQL dedicada</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podporuje návrh dotazov vo vyhradenom SQL pohľade</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för frågekonstruktion i en dedicerad SQL-vy</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка створення запитів за допомогою спеціальної панелі SQL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for query design in dedicated SQL viewxx</li>
      <li>Designing and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Izrada i prikazivanje relacijskih podataka pomoću combo kutije ( pregledavanje kolone)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Disseny i visualització de dades relacionals usant quadres combinats (columnes de cerca)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Disseny i visualització de dades relacionals usant quadres combinats (columnes de cerca)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Designing and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Diseño y presentación de datos relacionales utilizando listas desplegables (columnas de búsqueda)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Relatsiooniliste andmete kujundamine ja kuvamine liitkastide abil (päringuveerud)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Relaatiotiedon suunnittelu ja näyttö yhdistelmäkenttiä käyttäen (hakusarakkeet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Conception et affichage de données relationnelles à l'aide de listes déroulantes (colonnes de consultation)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Progettazione e visualizzazione dei dati relazionali utilizzando caselle combinate (colonne di ricerca)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">コンボボックスを使用した関係データのデザインと表示(参照列)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Utforming og visning av relasjonsdata vhja kombo-bokser (oppslagskolonner)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ontwerpen en tonen van relationele gegevens met gebruik van keuzelijsten (kolommen voor opzoeken)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Opracowywanie i wyświetlanie danych relacyjnych przy użyciu pól rozwijanych (kolumn wyszukiwania)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenho e apresentação de dados relacionais com listas (colunas de pesquisa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Desenho e apresentação de dados relacionais usando listas (colunas de pesquisa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Návrh a zobrazenie relačných dát pomocou combo boxov (lookup stĺpce)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Konstruktion och visning av relationsdata med användning av kombinationsrutor (uppslagning av kolumner)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення та показ пов’язаних даних за допомогою спадних списків (стовпчики пошуку).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDesigning and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)xx</li>
      <li>Direct data entry or import using CSV format</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Unos podataka direktno  ili uvoz pomoću CSV formata</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Entrada directa de dades o importació usant el format CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Entrada directa de dades o importació usant el format CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Direkte Dateneingabe oder Import aus dem CSV-Format</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Direct data entry or import using CSV format</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Entrada directa de datos o importación utilizando el formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Otsene andmete sisestamine või importimine CSV-vormingus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Suora tiedon syöttö tai tuonti CSV-muodossa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Saisie directe de données ou import utilisant le format CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Inserimento diretto dei dati o importazione utilizzando il formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">CSV を使用したダイレクトデータの入力もしくはインポート</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Direkte datainnskriving eller import med CSV-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Directe invoer van gegevens of importeren met het CSV-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Bezpośrednie wprowadzanie danych lub importowanie ich z postaci CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Introdução ou importação directa de dados com o formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Entrada ou importação direta de dados usando o formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Priamy vstup údajov alebo import pomocou formátu CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Direkt datainmatning eller import med CSV-format</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Безпосереднє введення даних або імпортування даних у форматі CSV.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDirect data entry or import using CSV formatxx</li>
      <li>Locked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's design</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Zatvoreni  korisnički režim, omogućavajući vam da isključite sve naredbe koje se odnose na uređivanje dizajna vašeg projekta</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mode reduït d'usuari, que permet deshabilitar totes les ordres relacionades amb l'edició del disseny del projecte</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mode reduït d'usuari, que permet deshabilitar totes les ordes relacionades amb l'edició del disseny del projecte</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Locked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's design</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Modo de usuario limitado, que permite desactivar todas las ordenes relacionadas con la edición del diseño de su proyecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Piiratud õigustega kasutajarežiim, mis võimaldab lülitada välja kõik projekti kujunduse muutmisega seotud käsud</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Lukittu käyttäjätila, jossa voit poistaa käytöstä projektin suunnitteluun liittyvät komennot</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Mode utilisateur verrouillé, vous permettant de désactiver toutes les commandes liées à la modification de la conception de votre projet</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Modalità utente bloccata, che ti consente di disattivare tutti i comandi in grado di modificare la struttura del tuo progetto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">プロジェクトデザインの編集スイッチをオフにする事でユーザモードへのロックダウンが可能</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Låst brukermodus, slik at du kan slå av alle kommandoer som gjelder endring av prosjektets utforming</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Vergrendelde gebruikersodus, waarmee u alle commando's uitschakelt die zijn gerelateerd aan bewerken en ontwerpen van uw project</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zamknięty tryb użytkownika, umożliwiający wyłączenie wszystkich poleceń związanych z edytowaniem twojego projektu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Modo reduzido de utilizador, permitindo-lhe desligar todos os comandos relacionados com a edição do desenho do seu projecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modo de usuário reduzido, permitindo-lhe desligar todos os comandos relacionados à edição do visual do seu projeto</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Uzamknutý používateľský režim, umožňujúci vám vypnúť všetky príkazy súvisiace s úpravou dizajnu vášho projektu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Låsbart användarläge, som låter dig stänga av alla kommandon relaterade till redigering av projektets konstruktion</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Заблокований режим користувача, у якому можна вимкнути усі пов’язані з командами редагування компонування вашого проекту команди.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLocked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's designxx</li>
      <li>Scripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Scripting koristeći JavaScript, Python ili Ruby programskim jezicima (eksperimentalno)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Crear scripts usant els llenguatges de programació JavaScript, Python o Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Crear scripts usant els llenguatges de programació JavaScript, Python o Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Skripte in den Programmsprachen JavaScript, Python oder Ruby (experimentell)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Scripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Programación de scripts escritos en los lenguajes de programación JavaScript, Python o Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Skriptimisvõimalused JavaScripti, Pythoni või Ruby programmeerimiskeeles (eksperimentaalne)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Skriptaus JavaScript-, Python- tai Ruby-ohjelmointikielillä (kokeellinen)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Pilotage par scripts utilisant les les langages JavaScript, Python ou Ruby (expérimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Creazione script utilizzando i linguaggi di programmazione JavaScript, Python o Ruby (sperimentale)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">JavaScript, Python や Ruby を使用してのスクリプティング(実験的)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nb">Skripting ved bruk av JavaScript, Python eller Ruby programmeringsspråk (eksperimentelt)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Scripting met de programmeertalen JavaScript, Python of Ruby (experimenteel)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Skrypty wykorzystujące języki programowania JavaScript, Python lub Ruby (eksperymentalnie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Programável através das linguagens JavaScript, Python ou Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de scripts usando as linguagens de programação JavaScript, Python ou Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Skriptovanie pomocou programovacích jazykov JavaScript, Python alebo Ruby (experimentálne)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skript med användning av programspråken Javascript, Python eller Ruby (experimentellt)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Керування за допомогою скриптів мовами JavaScript, Python та Ruby (експериментальна можливість).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.calligra.org/kexi/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kexi</url>
  <url type="help">http://userbase.kde.org/Kexi/Handbook</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/06/kexi-2.5-new-form-widgets.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Table View storing images</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bs">Tabela View čuvanje slika</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de taula emmagatzemant imatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de taula emmagatzemant imatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Tabellenansicht mit Bildern</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Table View storing images</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Una vista de tabla para almacenar imágenes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Tabelivaates piltide salvestamise võimalus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Kuvien tallennus taulukkonäkymään</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage de tables stockant des images</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista tabella per archiviare immagini</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">イメージを格納するテーブルビュー</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Tabellvisning som lagrer bilder</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Tabelweergave bij opslaan van afbeeldingen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Przechowywanie obrazów w widoku tabeli</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A área da tabela permite guardar as imagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Área da tabela armazenando imagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Tabuľkový pohľad uloženia obrázkov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tabellvy som lagrar bilder</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Збереження зображень у перегляді таблиць.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTable View storing imagesxx</caption>
      <image>http://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/kexi-2.2-rc1-tableview-images.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Form Designer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bs">Obrazac Designer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Dissenyador de formularis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Dissenyador de formularis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Formular-Designer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Form Designer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Diseñador de formularios</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Vormikujundaja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Lomakkeiden suunnittelu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Concepteur de formulaires</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Progettazione moduli</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">フォームデザイナー</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Skjemautformer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Ontwerper van formulieren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Opracowywanie formularzy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Desenhador de Formulários</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta de desenho de formulários</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Návrhár formulárov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Formulärkonstruktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Засіб для розробки форм.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxForm Designerxx</caption>
      <image>http://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/kexi-2.3-form.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligrakexi</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
