<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kexi.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kexi</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKexixx</name>
  <summary>Database Creator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Tvůrce databází</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Database aanmaken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Criador de Bases de Dados</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для створення баз даних</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDatabase Creatorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kexi is a visual database creator, part of the Calligra Suite.
      It can be used for designing database applications, inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data.
      Forms can be created to provide a custom interface to your data.
      All database objects - tables, queries, forms, reports - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kexi é um criador de bases de dados visuais, que faz parte do pacote Calligra. Pode ser usado para desenhar aplicações de bases de dados, inserir e editar dados, executar pesquisas e processar os dados. Poderá criar formulários para oferecer uma interface personalizada para os seus dados. Todos os objectos da base de dados - tabelas, pesquisas, formulários, relatórios - são guardados na base de dados, tornando simples a partilha e o desenho dos dados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kexi — програма для створення баз даних у візуальному режимі, частина комплексу програм Calligra. Цією програмою можна скористатися для створень мініпрограм для роботи з базами даних, додавання та редагування даних, виконання запитів та обробки даних. За допомогою створених програмою форм ви можете отримати потрібний вам режим доступу до ваших даних. Всі об’єкти баз даних — таблиці, запити, форми, звіти, — зберігаються у самій базі даних, що спрощує поширення даних та представлення даних.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKexi is a visual database creator, part of the Calligra Suite. It can be used for designing database applications, inserting and editing data, performing queries, and processing data. Forms can be created to provide a custom interface to your data. All database objects - tables, queries, forms, reports - are stored in the database, making it easy to share data and design.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Full visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reports</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenhadores visuais completos para tabelas, pesquisas, formulários e relatórios</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повноцінне візуальне середовище для створення таблиць, запитів, форм та звітів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull visual designers for tables, queries, forms and reportsxx</li>
      <li>Running queries, support for parametrized queries</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Execução de pesquisas, suporte para pesquisas parametrizadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Виконання запитів, підтримка параметризованих запитів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxRunning queries, support for parametrized queriesxx</li>
      <li>Supports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL and MS SQL Server databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt databases SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL en MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta bases de dados SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL e MS SQL Server</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка баз даних SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL та MS SQL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports SQLite, MySQL, PostgreSQL and MS SQL Server databasesxx</li>
      <li>The only multiplatform graphical tool importing data from MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Het enige multiplatform grafische hulpmiddel die gegevens importeert uit MS Access databases</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A única ferramenta gráfica multi-plataforma que consegue importar bases de dados MS Access</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Єдиний графічний багатоплатформовий інструмент, здатний імпортувати дані з баз даних MS Access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThe only multiplatform graphical tool importing data from MS Access databasesxx</li>
      <li>Supports query design in dedicated SQL view</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta o desenho de pesquisas numa área de SQL dedicada</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка створення запитів за допомогою спеціальної панелі SQL.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports query design in dedicated SQL viewxx</li>
      <li>Designing and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Desenho e apresentação de dados relacionais com listas (colunas de pesquisa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення та показ пов’язаних даних за допомогою спадних списків (стовпчики пошуку).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDesigning and displaying relational data using combo boxes (lookup columns)xx</li>
      <li>Direct data entry or import using CSV format</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Introdução ou importação directa de dados com o formato CSV</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Безпосереднє введення даних або імпортування даних у форматі CSV.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDirect data entry or import using CSV formatxx</li>
      <li>Locked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's design</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Modo reduzido de utilizador, permitindo-lhe desligar todos os comandos relacionados com a edição do desenho do seu projecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Заблокований режим користувача, у якому можна вимкнути усі пов’язані з командами редагування компонування вашого проекту команди.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLocked down User Mode, allowing you to switch off all commands related to editing your project's designxx</li>
      <li>Scripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Programável através das linguagens JavaScript, Python ou Ruby (experimental)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Керування за допомогою скриптів мовами JavaScript, Python та Ruby (експериментальна можливість).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScripting using JavaScript, Python or Ruby programming languages (experimental)xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.calligra.org/kexi/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kexi</url>
  <url type="help">http://userbase.kde.org/Kexi/Handbook</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kexi.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Table View storing images</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A área da tabela permite guardar as imagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Збереження зображень у перегляді таблиць.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTable View storing imagesxx</caption>
      <image>http://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/kexi-2.2-rc1-tableview-images.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Form Designer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Desenhador de Formulários</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Засіб для розробки форм.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxForm Designerxx</caption>
      <image>http://www.calligra.org/wp-content/uploads/2011/11/kexi-2.3-form.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligrakexi</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
