<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>stage.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Stage</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Stage</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Stage</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Stage</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxStagexx</name>
  <summary>Presentation</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Prezentace</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Apresentação</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Презентації</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPresentationxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Calligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application.
      You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system,
      so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility
      of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Calligra Stage é uma aplicação de apresentações simples de usar, mas também bastante flexível. Poderá criar facilmente apresentações que contêm uma grande variedade de elementos, desde gráficos a texto, assim como de gráficos a imagens. O Calligra Stage é modular através de um sistema de 'plugins', pelo que é fácil adicionar novos efeitos, elementos de conteúdo ou até novas formas de gerir a sua apresentação. Devido à integração com o Calligra, todo o poder e flexibilidade dos elementos de conteúdo do Calligra estão disponíveis no Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Calligra Stage — проста, але потужна програма для роботи з презентаціями. За її допомогою ви без проблем зможете створити презентацію з багатим набором елементів, від графіки до тексту, від діаграм до зображень. Можливості Calligra Stage можна розширити за допомогою системи додатків: ви можете додати нові ефекти, нові елементи вмісту і навіть нові способи керування презентацією. Через тісну інтеграцію з рештою програм Calligra ви можете скористатися усіма потужними та гнучкими елементами решти програм Calligra безпосередньо у Stage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Stage is an easy to use yet still flexible presentation application. You can easily create presentations containing a rich variety of elements, from graphics to text, from charts to images. Calligra Stage is extensible through a plugin system, so it is easy to add new effects, new content elements or even new ways of managing your presentation. Because of the integration with Calligra, all the power and flexibility of the Calligra content elements are available to Stage.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Multiple master slides</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diversos 'slides'-mestres</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Використання декількох основних слайдів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMultiple master slidesxx</li>
      <li>Easily switch between slides during a presentation</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mudar facilmente de 'slides' durante uma apresentação</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Просте перемикання між слайдами під час презентації.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEasily switch between slides during a presentationxx</li>
      <li>Add notes for your slide</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Adicionar notas ao seu 'slide'</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Додавання нотаток до слайдів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAdd notes for your slidexx</li>
      <li>Supports most ODF file transitions</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a maioria das transições nos ficheiros ODF</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка більшості переходів у файлах ODF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports most ODF file transitionsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.calligra.org/stage/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=calligrastage</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/calligra/stage/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/stage.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligrastage</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
