<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>flow.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Flow (Fluxo)</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Przepływ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Flow</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxFlowxx</name>
  <summary>Flowchart &amp; Diagram Editing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Edició de diagrames de fluxos i diagrames</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Modifica de diagramma de fluxo &amp; diagramma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Diagrammi di flusso e modifica di diagrammi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Bewerking van stroomdiagrammen &amp; grafieken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytowanie wykresów przepływu i diagramów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Edição de Fluxogramas &amp; Diagramas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Edição de fluxogramas e diagramas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Vývojový diagram &amp; úprava diagramu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Flödesdiagram och diagramredigering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редагування блок-схем і діаграм</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxFlowchart &amp; Diagram Editingxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Calligra Flow is an easy to use diagramming and flowcharting application with tight integration to the other Calligra applications.
      It enables you to create network diagrams, organisation charts, flowcharts and more.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Calligra Flow és una aplicació fàcil d'utilitzar per fer diagrames i diagrames de flux amb una estreta integració amb altres aplicacions del Calligra. Permet crear diagrames de xarxa, diagrames d'organització, diagrames de flux i més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Calligra Flow es un application facile de usar pro facer diagrammas e diagrammas de fluxo con un forte integration con altere applicationes de Calligra. Illo permitte te crear diagrammas de rete, graphicos de organisation, diagrammas de fluxo e alteres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Calligra Flow è un'applicazione di facile utilizzo per creare diagrammi di flusso e altro con una stretta integrazione con le altre applicazioni di Calligra. Ti consente di creare diagrammi di rete, organigrammi, diagrammi di flusso e altro.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Calligra Flow is een gemakkelijk te gebruiken toepassing voor het maken van diagrammen en flowcharts met nauwe integratie met de andere toepassingen van Calligra. Het stelt u in staat om netwerkdiagrammen, organisatiediagrammen, flowcharts en meer te maken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Przepływ Calligra jest łatwym w użyciu programem do rysowania diagramów i wykresów przepływu, będącym ściśle powiązanym z innymi programami Calligra. Umożliwia tworzenie diagramów sieciowych, wykresów organizacyjnych, wykresów przepływów i innych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Calligra Flow é uma aplicação de diagramas e fluxogramas com uma integração forte com as outras aplicações do Calligra. Permite-lhe criar diagramas de rede, organigramas, fluxogramas, entre outros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Calligra Flow é um aplicativo para criação de diagramas e fluxogramas fácil de usar e com uma forte integração com as outros aplicativos do Calligra. Permite-lhe criar diagramas de rede, organogramas, fluxogramas, entre outros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Calligra Flow je ľahko použiteľná aplikácia na diagramy a vývojové diagramy s úzkou integráciou s inými aplikáciami Calligra. Umožní vám vytvárať sieťové diagramy, organizačné schémy, vývojové diagramy a viac.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Calligra Flow är ett lättanvänt program för att skapa diagram och flödesdiagram med nära integration med övriga program i Calligra. Det möjliggör att skapa nätverksdiagram, organisationsdiagram, flödesdiagram med mera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Calligra Flow — проста у користуванні програма для створення діаграм та блок-схем з тісною інтеграцією з іншими програмами Calligra. За її допомогою ви можете створювати мережеві діаграми, організаційні діаграми, блок-схеми тощо.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCalligra Flow is an easy to use diagramming and flowcharting application with tight integration to the other Calligra applications. It enables you to create network diagrams, organisation charts, flowcharts and more.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Create network diagrams, organisation charts, flowcharts and more</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Crea diagrames de xarxa, diagrames d'organització, diagrames de flux i més</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Crea diagrammas de rete, graphicos de organisation, diagrammas de fluxo e alteres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Crea diagrammi di rete, organigrammi, diagrammi di flusso e altro</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Netwerkdiagrammen, organisatiediagrammen, stroomdiagrammen en meer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie diagramów sieciowych, wykresów organizacyjnych, wykresów przepływów i innych.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Criar diagramas de rede, organigramas, fluxogramas, entre outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Criar diagramas de rede, organogramas, fluxogramas, entre outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vytváranie sieťových diagramov, organizačných schém, vývojových diagramov a viac</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skapa nätverksdiagram, organisationsdiagram, flödesdiagram med mera</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення мережевих діаграм, організаційних діаграм, блок-схем тощо.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCreate network diagrams, organisation charts, flowcharts and morexx</li>
      <li>Scriptable stencil creation using Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Creació de patrons amb scripts usant el Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Creation de stencil de script usante Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Creazione forme con script utilizzando Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Maken van stencils met scripts met Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tworzenie wzorców skryptowych przy użyciu Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Criação de formas programáveis com o Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Criação de formas programáveis usando Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Skriptovateľné vytváranie šablón pomocou Pythonu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att skapa stenciler med skript genom att använda Python</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Створення шаблонів на основі скриптів мовою Python.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScriptable stencil creation using Pythonxx</li>
      <li>Support for Dia stencils.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementació de patrons del Dia</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporto pro stencils de Dia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta le forme di Dia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor Dia-stencils.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa wzorców Dia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para formas do Dia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para formas do Dia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora pre Dia šablóny.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för Dia-stenciler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка шаблонів Dia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for Dia stencils.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.calligra.org/flow/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=calligraflow</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/flow.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligraflow</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
