<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>karbon.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Karbon</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKarbonxx</name>
  <summary>Scalable Graphics</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gràfics escalables</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Škálovatelná grafika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Graphicos scalabile</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Grafica scalabile</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Vectorafbeeldingen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Skalowalna grafika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gráficos Vectoriais</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Imagens vetoriais</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Škálovateľná grafika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Skalbar grafik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для роботи з масштабованою графікою</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxScalable Graphicsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Karbon is a vector drawing application with an user interface that is easy to use, highly customizable and extensible.
      That makes Karbon a great application for users starting to explore the world of vector graphics as well as for artists
      wanting to create breathtaking vector art.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Karbon és una aplicació de dibuix vectorial amb una interfície d'usuari senzilla d'utilitzar, que es pot personalitzar i ampliar molt. Això converteix el Karbon en una gran aplicació per usuaris que comencin a explorar el món dels gràfics vectorial i també pels artistes que volen crear art vectorial que deixi bocabadat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Karbon è un'applicazione di disegno vettoriale con un'interfaccia utente facile da utilizzare, altamente personalizzabile ed estendibile. Ciò rende Karbon una grande applicazione per gli utenti che iniziano a esplorare il mondo della grafica vettoriale così come per gli artisti che vogliono creare staordinare opere vettoriali. </p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Karbon is een toepassing voor tekenen met vectoren met een gebruikersinterface dat gemakkelijk is te gebruiken, zeer goed aan te passen en uit te breiden. Dit maakt Karbon een geweldige toepassing voor gebruikers die de wereld van grafiek met vectoren aan het verkennen zijn evenals voor kunstenaars die adembenemende vectorkunst willen maken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Karbon jest programem do rysowania wektorowego z układem sterowania, który jest łatwy w użyciu, wysoce dostosowywalny i rozszerzalny. To czyni Karbon wspaniałym programem dla użytkowników zaczynających poznawanie świata grafiki wektorowej, a artystów zachęca do tworzenie sztuki wektorowej zapierającej dech w piersiach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Karbon é uma aplicação de desenho vectorial com uma interface simples de usar, facilmente configurável e modular. Isto torna o Karbon uma óptima aplicação para os utilizadores que começam a explorar o mundo dos gráficos vectoriais, assim como para os artistas que desejam criar arte vectorial espectacular.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Karbon é um aplicativo de desenho vetorial com uma interface simples de usar, facilmente configurável e expansível. Isso torna o Karbon um ótimo aplicativo para usuários que começam a explorar o mundo dos gráficos vetoriais, assim como para artistas que desejam criar arte vetorial espetacular.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Karbon je vektorová kresliaca aplikácia s používateľským rozhraním jednoduchým na používanie, veľmi prispôsobiteľná a rozšíriteľná. Toto robí z Karbonu výbornú aplikáciu pre používateľov, ktorí začínajú objavovať sveet vektorovej grafiky, ako aj pre umelcov, ktorí chcú vytvárať dych vyrážajúce vektorové umenie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Karbon är ett vektorritprogram med ett användargränssnitt som är lätt att använda, ytterst anpassningsbart och utökningsbart. Det gör Karbon till ett utmärkt program för användare som börjar utforska vektorgrafikvärlden samt för konstnärer som vill skapa hänförande vektorkonst.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Karbon — програма для векторного малювання з простим, гнучким та придатним до розширення інтерфейсом користувача. Це робить Karbon чудовою програмою для користувачів, які починають знайомитися зі світом векторної графіки, а також для художників, які хочуть створити захоплюючі векторні твори.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKarbon is a vector drawing application with an user interface that is easy to use, highly customizable and extensible. That makes Karbon a great application for users starting to explore the world of vector graphics as well as for artists wanting to create breathtaking vector art.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>
        Loading support for ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet llegir ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Cargante supporto pro ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per il caricamento di ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor laden van ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa wczytywania dla ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte do carregamento de imagens em ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para carregamento de ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora čítania pre ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för att läsa in ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка завантаження даних ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PS.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLoading support for ODG, SVG, WPG, WMF, EPS/PSxx</li>
      <li>
        Writing support for ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet gravar ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporto de scriber pro ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per la scrittura di ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor schrijven van ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa zapisywania dla ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte da gravação de imagens em ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte de gravação em ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora zápisu pre ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för att skriva ut ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка запису у форматах ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMF.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWriting support for ODG, SVG, PNG, PDF, WMFxx</li>
      <li>
        Customizable user interface with freely placeable toolbars and dockers2
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Interfície d'usuari que es pot personalitzar que permet situar lliurement barres d'eines i acobladors</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Personalisa le interfacie de usator con barra de instrumentos e stivatores (dockers) liberemente positionabile</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Interfaccia utente personalizzabile con barre degli strumenti posizionabili liberamente e aree di aggancio</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Aan te passen gebruikersinterface met vrij te plaatsen werkbalken en dockers2</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Układ sterowania z dowolnie umieszczanymi paskami narzędzi i dokowaniami</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Interface de utilizador configurável com barras e áreas acopláveis livres</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Interface de usuário configurável com barras e áreas acopláveis livres</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nastaviteľné používateľské rozhranie s voľne umiestniteľnými panelmi nástrojov a dockermi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anpassningsbart användargränssnitt med verktygsrader och paneler som kan placeras fritt</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Придатний до налаштовування інтерфейс користувача з довільним розташуванням панелей інструментів та бічних панелей.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCustomizable user interface with freely placeable toolbars and dockers2xx</li>
      <li>
        Layer docker for easy handling of complex documents including preview thumbnails, support for grouping shapes via
        drag and drop, controlling visibility of shapes or locking
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Acoblador de capa per a una gestió senzilla de documents complexos incloent la vista prèvia de miniatures, permet agrupar formes via arrossegar i deixar anar, controlar la visibilitat de les formes o el bloqueig.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Laagverankering voor gemakkelijke behandeling van complexe documenten inclusief voorbeeldminiaturen, ondersteuning voor groeperen van vormen via slepen en laten vallen, besturing van zichtbaarheid van vormen of vastzetten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dokowanie warstw dla łatwiejszej obsługi złożonych dokumentów zawierający: podgląd miniatur, obsługę grupowania kształtów poprzez przeciągnij i upuść, sterowanie widocznością kształtów czy blokowanie.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Área de camadas para o tratamento de documentos complexos, incluindo miniaturas da antevisão, suporte para o agrupamento de formas por arrastamento, o controlo da visibilidade das formas ou o seu bloqueio</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Área de camadas para tratamento de documentos complexos, incluindo miniaturas, suporte a agrupamento de formas com arrastar e soltar, controle de visibilidade das formas ou seu bloqueio</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Docker vrstiev pre ľahkú manipuláciu so zložitými dokumentami vrátane náhľadu miniatúr, podpora pre zoskupovanie tvarov cez drag and drop, ovládanie viditeľnosti tvarov alebo zamykanie</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Lagerpanel för enkel hantering av komplexa dokument inklusive miniatyrbilder för förhandsgranskning, stöd för att gruppera former via drag och släpp, styra eller låsning synlighet av former</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Панель шарів для полегшення обробки складних документів з мініатюрами об’єктів, підтримка групування форм перетягуванням зі скиданням, керування показом форм та блокуванням.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLayer docker for easy handling of complex documents including preview thumbnails, support for grouping shapes via drag and drop, controlling visibility of shapes or lockingxx</li>
      <li>
        Advanced path editing tool with great on-canvas editing capabilities
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Eina avançada d'edició de camins amb una grana capacitat d'edició en el llenç</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Geavanceerde padbewerkingsgereedschap met prima bewerkingsmiddelen op het werkblad</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zaawansowane narzędzia edytowania ścieżki z szerokimi możliwościami edytowania na płótnie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ferramenta de edição de caminhos avançada, com grandes capacidade de edição no local</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta de edição de caminhos avançada, com ótima capacidade de edição no local</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Pokročilý nástroj na úpravu ciest s výbornými schopnosťami editácie na plátne</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Avancerat konturredigeringsverktyg med utmärkta redigeringsmöjligheter direkt på duken</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інструмент редагування контурів з чудовими можливостями редагування безпосередньо на полотні.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAdvanced path editing tool with great on-canvas editing capabilitiesxx</li>
      <li>
        Various drawing tools for creating path shapes including a draw path tool, a pencil tool as well as a calligraphy drawing tool
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Diverses eines de dibuix per crear formes de camí incloent una eina de dibuix de camins, una eina de llapis i també una eina de dibuix de cal·ligrafia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Vari strumenti di disegno per creare percorsi e forme che include uno strumento di tracciati, un matita e uno strumento calligrafico</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verschillende tekengereedschappen voor het maken van padvormen inclusief een tekenhulpmiddel voor paden, een potloodhulpmiddel evenals een tekengereedschap voor kalligrafie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Różne narzędzia rysownicze do tworzenia kształtów ścieżek uwzględniając w tym: narzędzie rysowania ścieżki, narzędzie ołówka, a także kaligraficzne narzędzia rysownicze </li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diversas ferramentas de desenho para criar formas de caminhos, incluindo uma ferramenta de desenho de caminhos, uma ferramenta de lápis e uma ferramenta de desenho caligráfico</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Diversas ferramentas de desenho para criar formas de caminhos, incluindo uma ferramenta de desenho de caminhos, uma ferramenta de lápis e uma ferramenta de desenho caligráfico</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rôzne kresliace nástroje na vytváranie tvarov ciest vrátane nástroja na kreslenie cesty, nástroja ceruzky ako aj kaligrafického kresliaceho nástroja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Diverse ritverktyg för att skapa konturformer som inkluderar ett konturritverktyg, ett pennverktyg samt ett kalligrafiskt ritverktyg</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Різноманітні інструменти малювання для створення контурів, зокрема інструмент малювання контуру, олівець та інструмент каліграфічного малювання.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxVarious drawing tools for creating path shapes including a draw path tool, a pencil tool as well as a calligraphy drawing toolxx</li>
      <li>
        Gradient and pattern tools for easy on-canvas editing of gradient and pattern styles
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Eines de degradats i patrons per a una edició senzilla sobre el llenç d'estils de degradats i patrons</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Hulpmiddelen voor gradiënten en patronen voor gemakkelijk werken op het werkblad van gradiënten en patroonstijlen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Narzędzia gradientu i wzorca dla łatwiejszego ich edytowania na płótnie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ferramentas de gradientes e padrões para uma edição simples no local dos estilos dos gradientes e dos padrões</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramentas de gradientes e padrões para fácil edição no local dos estilos dos gradientes e dos padrões</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nástroje na prechody a vzory pre ľahké editovanie na plátne štýlov prechodov a vzorov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tonings- och mönsterverktyg för enkelt redigering av tonings- och mönsterstilar direkt på duken</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інструменти градієнта і візерунка для полегшення редагування на полотні областей з заповненням градієнтом і візерунком.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxGradient and pattern tools for easy on-canvas editing of gradient and pattern stylesxx</li>
      <li>
        Top notch snapping facilities for guided drawing and editing (e.g. snapping to grid, guide lines, path nodes, bounding boxes,
        orthogonal positions, intersections of path shapes or extensions of lines and paths)
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Capacitats òptimes d'ajust per dibuix guiat i edició (p.e. ajust a graella, línies de guia, nodes de camins, caixes contenidores, posicions ortogonals, interseccions de formes de camí o extensions de línies i camins)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Excellente vastklik faciliteiten voor geleid tekenen en bewerken (bijv. vastklikken aan raster, gidslijnen, padpunten, begrenzingsvakken, orthogonale posities, kruispunten van padvormen of extensies van lijnen en paden)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwości przyciągania z najwyższej półki rysowania i edytowania ze wspomaganiem (np. przyciąganie do siatki, -prowadnic, węzłów ścieżki, pól ograniczających, prostopadłych położeń, przecięć kształtów ścieżek lub wydłużeń linii i ścieżek)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidades de ajuste óptimas para o desenho e edição guiado (p.ex., ajustes à grelha, linhas-guias, nós de caminhos, áreas envolventes, posições ortogonais, intersecções de formas de caminhos ou extensões de linhas e caminhos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidades de melhor ajuste para desenho e edição guiado (p.ex., ajustes à grade, linhas-guias, nós de caminhos, caixas delimitadoras, posições ortogonais, intersecções de formas de caminhos ou extensões de linhas e caminhos)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schopnosti prichytenia na vrch pre sprevádzané kreslenie a editovanie (napr. prichytenie k mriežke, pomocné čiary, uzly cesty, hraničné boxy, ortogonálne polohy, priesečníky tvarov cesty alebo rozšírenia čiar a ciest)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Väldigt bra låsfunktioner för att rita och redigera med styrning (t.ex. låsa till rutnät, styrlinjer, konturnoder, omgivande rutor, ortogonala positioner, korsningar av konturformer eller förlängningar av linjer och konturer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливості використання прилипання та малювання за напрямними (прилипання до сітки, напрямні, вузли контурів, обмежувальні рамки, ортогональне розташування, перетини та розширення ліній і контурів).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTop notch snapping facilities for guided drawing and editing (e.g. snapping to grid, guide lines, path nodes, bounding boxes, orthogonal positions, intersections of path shapes or extensions of lines and paths)xx</li>
      <li>
        Includes many predefined shapes including basic shapes like stars, circle/ellipse, rectangle, image
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Inclou moltes formes predefinides bàsiques com estels, cercles/el·lipses, rectangles, imatges</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Include molte forme predefinite tra cui forme base come stelle, cerchi/ellissi, rettangoli e immagini</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Omvat vele voorgedefinieerde vormen inclusief basisvormen als ster, cirkel/ellips, rechthoek, afbeelding</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zawiera wiele uprzednio stworzonych kształtów, do których można zaliczyć gwiazdy, okręgi, elipsy, prostokąty, obrazy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Inclui diversas formas predefinidas, incluindo formas básicas como as estrelas, círculos/elipses, rectângulos, imagens</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Inclui diversas formas predefinidas, incluindo formas básicas como estrelas, círculos/elipses, retângulos, imagens</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Obsahuje mnoho preddefinovaných tvarov vrátane základných tvarov ako hviezdy, kružnica/elipsa, obdĺžnik, obrázok</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Innehåller många fördefinierade former inklusive grundläggande former som stjärnor, cirkel/ellips, rektangel, bild</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Передбачено багато готових форм, зокрема базові форми зірки, кола або еліпса, прямокутника та зображення.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxIncludes many predefined shapes including basic shapes like stars, circle/ellipse, rectangle, imagexx</li>
      <li>
        Artistic text shape with support for following path outlines (i.e. text on path)
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Formes de text artístic que permeten camins de contorns de seguiment (p.e. text en camins)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Forme di testo artistico con supporto per le bordature che seguono il tracciato (ad es. testo su tracciato)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Artistieke tekstvormen met ondersteuning voor het volden van paden (dwz. tekst op een pad)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kształty artystycznego tekstu z obsługą dla następujących zarysów ścieżek (tj. tekst na ścieżce)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Forma de texto artístico com suporte para caminhos de seguimento (i.e., texto ao longo de um caminho)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Forma de texto artístico com suporte para caminhos de seguimento (isto é, texto no caminho)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Umelecký textový tvar s podporou pre nasledovacie obrysy cesty (napr. text na ceste)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Artistisk textform med stöd för att följa konturlinjer (t.ex. text på en kontur)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Форма художнього тексту для розташування тексту вздовж контуру.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxArtistic text shape with support for following path outlines (i.e. text on path)xx</li>
      <li>
        Complex path operations and effects like boolean set operations, path flattening, rounding and refining as well as whirl/pinch effects
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Operacions complexes de camins i efectes com operacions de conjunts booleans, aplanament de camins, arrodoniment i afinació i també efectes de gir i pessic</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Complexe bewerkingen van paden en effecten zoals booleaanse set bewerkingen, afvlakken van paden, afronding en verfijning evenals wervel/put-effecten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Złożone działania i efekty na ścieżce takie jak działania boolean, spłaszczanie ścieżki, zaokrąglanie, a także efekty polepszające wraz z efektami wiru/rozdmuchania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Opções complexas com caminhos e efeitos como as operações booleanas com conjuntos, o alisamento de caminhos, o arredondamento e a afinação, para além da ondulação/embate</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Operações complexas com caminhos e efeitos, como operações booleanas com conjuntos, o nivelamento de caminhos, o arredondamento e refinamento, assim como efeitos de ondulação/aperto</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Komplexné cestné operácie a efekty ako logické operácie, splošťovanie cesty, zaobľovanie a zjemňovanie ako aj efekty vírov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Komplexa konturoperationer och effekter som Booleska mängdoperationer, konturutplattning, rundning och förfining samt virvla- och klämeffekter</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Складні дії над контурами та ефекти, зокрема набір булівських операцій, спрощення контуру, заокруглення та покращення, ефекти вихору та втягування</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxComplex path operations and effects like boolean set operations, path flattening, rounding and refining as well as whirl/pinch effectsxx</li>
      <li>
        Extensible by writing plugins for new tools, shapes and dockers
      </li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Ampliable mitjançant l'escriptura de connectors per eines noves, formes i acobladors</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Espandibile tramite la scrittura di estensioni per nuovi strumenti, forme e aree di aggancio</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uit te breiden dor het schrijven van plug-ins voor nieuwe hulpmiddelen, vormen en verankering</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Rozszerzalne wtyczki zapisu dla nowych narzędzi, kształtów i dokowań</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Modular, através da criação de 'plugins' para novas ferramentas, formas e áreas acopláveis</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Expansível através da criação de plugins para novas ferramentas, formas e áreas acopláveis</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rozšíriteľný pomocou písania pluginov pre nové nástroje, tvary a dockery</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Utökningsbart genom att skriva insticksprogram för nya verktyg, former och paneler</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість розширення додатками нових інструментів, форм та панелей.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxExtensible by writing plugins for new tools, shapes and dockersxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.calligra.org/karbon/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=karbon</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/karbon14.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>calligrakarbon</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
